http://www.wessex.ac.uk/privacy-policy

Search
HomeWIT ConferencesCoursesWebinarsResearchResearch StudiesPrigogine AwardAboutNewsContact Us
Wessex Institute
HomeWIT Conferences2021 Sustainable Water Resources Management 2021Water and Society 2021CMEM 2021ERES 2021STREMAH 2021BEM/MRM 44Urban and Maritime Transport 2021AFM/MPF 2021Materials Characterisation 2021Air Pollution 2021BIM 2021Sustainable City 2021Energy and Sustainability 20212020 Air Pollution 2020Islamic Heritage 2020Environmental Impact 2020Energy Production and Management 2020SUSI 2020Risk Analysis 2020COMPRAIL 2020Waste Management 2020Sustainable Tourism 2020AFM 2020HPSM/OPTI 2020Eco-Architecture 2020Urban Transport 2020BEM/MRM 432019 Water Resources Management
2019River Basin Management 2019Multiphase Flow 2019Materials Characterisation 2019CMEM 2019ERES 2019Urban Transport 2019Air Pollution 2019BEM/MRM 42Energy and Sustainability 2019Maritime Transport 2019Coastal Cities 2019SAFE 2019Disaster Management 2019Sustainable City 2019Water and Society 2019STREMAH 2019BIM 20192018 Islamic Heritage 2018 Sustainable Tourism 2018 Urban Growth 2018
Complex Systems 2018 Water Pollution 2018 FRIAR 2018 SUSI 2018 Risk Analysis 2018
Air Pollution 2018
Environmental Impact 2018
COMPRAIL 2018
AFM 2018
HPSM/OPTI 2018 Sustainable Development and Planning 2018 Energy Quest 2018BEM/MRM 41Waste Management 2018Urban Transport 2018Eco-Architecture 2018 Urban Agriculture 2018
2017 Coastal Cities 2017Air Pollution 2017ECOSUD 2017STREMAH 2017BIM 2017Complex Systems 2017Water and Society 2017Disaster Management 2017Timber Structures 2017Multiphase Flow 2017Materials Characterisation 2017Sustainable Development and Planning 2017CMEM 2017ERES 2017Water Resources Management 2017River Basin Management 2017Urban Transport 2017SAFE 2017BEM/MRM 40Sustainable City 2017Energy and Sustainability 20172016 Big Data 2016Defence Heritage 2016Islamic Heritage Architecture 2016Sustainable Tourism 2016SUSI 2016Risk Analysis 2016Complex Systems 2016Waste Management 2016Environmental Impact 2016Air Pollution 2016Urban Transport 2016Urban Water 2016Water Pollution 2016FRIAR 2016Sustainable City 2016Eco-Architecture 2016COMPRAIL 2016AFM 2016Energy Quest 2016Heat Transfer 2016Design & Nature 2016HPSM/OPTI 2016BEM/MRM 39MARAS 2016Sustainable Development and Planning 20162015 Multiphase Flow 2015Contact and Surface 2015Materials Characterisation 2015CMEM 2015SAFE 2015Complex Systems 2015Sustainable Development and Planning 2015Disaster Management 2015Air Pollution 2015Urban Transport 2015ECOSUD 2015Water Resources Management 2015River Basin Management 2015ERES 2015Ravage of the Planet IVCoastal Cities 2015STREMAH 2015Water and Society 2015Sustainable City 2015Energy and Sustainability 2015BIM 2015BEM/MRM 382014 Energy Quest 2014Waste Management 2014Environmental Impact 2014Water Pollution 2014Urban Water 2014Urban Transport 2014SUSI 2014Risk Analysis 2014HPSM/OPTI 2014MARAS 2014Sustainable Irrigation 2014FRIAR 2014COMPRAIL 2014AFM 2014Heat Transfer 2014Air Pollution 2014Sustainable Tourism 2014Design and Nature 2014BEM/MRM 37Defence Heritage 2014Sustainable City 2014Eco-Architecture 2014Energy and Sustainability 20142013 Coastal Processes 2013Fluid Structure Interaction 2013Food and Environment 2013Environmental Health Risk 2013BIOMED 2013DATA 2013Water Resources Management 2013River Basin Management 2013Sustainable Development and Planning 2013Urban Transport 2013Air Pollution 2013Materials Characterisation 2013Contact and Surface 2013BEM / MRM 2013ECOSUD 2013Energy and Sustainability 2013STREMAH 2013CMEM 2013Multiphase Flow 2013ERES 2013Disaster Management 2013Water and Society 2013SAFE 2013BEM/MRM 36Sustainable City 20132012 Urban Water 2012Sustainable City 2012Urban Transport 2012Air Pollution 2012Forest Fires 2012Debris Flow 2012FRIAR 2012Defence Sites: Heritage and Future 2012Design and Nature 2012Sustainable Tourism 2012HPSM 2012OPTI 2012BEM/MRM 2012AFM 2012Heat Transfer 2012Environmental Impact 2012Waste Management 2012Water Pollution 2012Tribology and Design 2012SUSI 2012Eco-Architecture 2012COMPRAIL 2012Islands 2012Risk Analysis 2012Petroleum 2012Sustainable Irrigation 20122011 Energy 2011ECOSUD 2011Coastal Processes 2011Fluid Structure Interaction 2011Disaster Management 2011Light 2011Water Resources Management 2011River Basin Management 2011CMEM 2011Urban Transport 2011Materials Characterisation 2011Multiphase Flow 2011Food and Environment 2011BEM/MRM 2011SAFE 2011Sustainable Chemistry 2011Sustainable Development and Planning 2011Environmental Health Risk 2011BIOMED 2011STREMAH 2011ERES 2011Lake Sustainability 2011Air Pollution 2011Contact and Surface 2011Water and Society 2011Ravage of the Planet 20112010 Eco-Architecture 2010The Sustainable City 2010Islands 2010Environmental Economics 2010Environmental Toxicology 2010Urban Transport 2010Tribology and Design 2010Debris Flow 2010FRIAR 2010Sustainable Irrigation 2010Water Pollution 2010Air Pollution 2010Forest Fires 2010Design and Nature 2010Sustainable Tourism 2010Waste Management 2010Heat Transfer 2010HPSM 2010SUSI 2010COMPRAIL 2010BEM / MRM 32Risk Analysis 2010Brownfields 2010AFM 20102009 ERES 2009Sustainable Development 2009Fluid Structure Interaction 2009BIOMED 2009Data Mining 2009OPTI 2009Contact/Surface 2009CMEM 2009Multiphase Flow 2009Materials Characterisation 2009Urban Transport 2009Energy and Sustainability 2009ELECTROCOR 2009SAFE 2009ECOSUD 2009Air Pollution 2009STREMAH 2009BEM/MRM 31River Basin Management 2009Water Resources Management 2009Coastal Processes 2009Environmental Health Risk 2009Disaster Management 2009Regional Airports SeminarRavage of the Planet 20092008 Risk Analysis 2008Brownfields 2008HPSM 2008SUSI 2008Coastal Environment 2008AFM 2008Data Mining 2008Computational Finance 2008Environmental Economics 2008Waste Management 2008Environmental Toxicology 2008Water Pollution 2008Sustainable Irrigation 2008Geo-Environment 2008Debris Flow 2008Eco-Architecture 2008Design and Nature 2008FRIAR 2008BEM/MRM 30Heat Transfer 2008Urban Transport 2008Sustainable Tourism 2008Underground Spaces 2008COMPRAIL 2008Forest Fires 2008Air Pollution 2008The Sustainable City 2008CoursesWebinarsResearchResearch StudiesPrigogine AwardAboutNewsContact Us
About WIT
AboutObituary - Professor Carlos A. BrebbiaChairman's MessageCOVID-19 Update - 2020 Conference Programme overview from our Chief Academic OfficerBoard of DirectorsCore ActivitiesAmerican OfficeInternational Conference ProgrammePublishing ActivitiesSoftware ServicesAccommodationCareersContact UsPrivacy Policy
Privacy Policy
This privacy policy sets out how Wessex Institute of Technology collects, uses and protects any information that you give us when you use our website or contact us directly. As the data controller Wessex Institute of Technology is committed to ensuring that the privacy of your personal information is protected.
1. The information we collect
We may collect the following information:
Your name, address and the name and address of your organisation.
Additional contact information including email address and telephone number.
Information about your professional areas of interest and details of any article, paper or book submissions you have made to us, including any biographical information.
Information specific to your visits to our websites including the IP address of the computer used, the browser used and pages visited.
2. How we use your information
Your information will be used to provide any services you have requested from us and to notify you of any events, activities or publications that we believe are within your area of interest.
Our preferred contact method is email, but we may also contact you by post or telephone.
We do not make use of automated decision making but endeavour to send you information based on your area of work, past attendance or interest in our events, activities or publications.
With the exception of our publisher “WIT Press” we will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we are required by law.
We may analyse the information specific to your visits to our websites in combination with other visitors to our websites to monitor and improve our websites.
3. Legal Basis for processing your personal data
The GDPR (General Data Protection Regulation (EU) 2016/679) requires that your personal data is only processed if there is a legal basis for the processing, the legal basis under which we are processing your data are:
a) Contract, if we are supplying you with a service, such as attendance to a conference or course you are entering into a contract for our services, and in order to fulfil our obligations under this contract we must be able to store and process your data. This will also apply if you make an enquiry or submit a request to attend a conference or course but do not make payment or do not attend.
b) Legitimate Interest, we are pursuing our legitimate interest to promote Wessex Institute of Technology stated objective to enable knowledge transfer by informing specific contacts about events that we believe will be of interest. This does not infringe your rights below which can be exercised at any time by contacting us.
4. Your rights
The GDPR sets out a number of rights that you have regarding your personal information.
a) The right to be informed. We will review and update this privacy policy from time to time to ensure that it remains accurate. Please review this privacy policy on a regular basis.
b) You have the right to access the personal information we hold about you. You may request a copy of your data, for which a fee is not normally charged, by emailing us at: This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it. or writing to our registered address below.
c) You have the right of rectification. If you believe that any information we hold on you is incorrect or incomplete, please inform us as soon as possible. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
d) You have the right to erasure. If you no longer wish us to hold your personal information we will fully comply with this request except for any invoices or other data that is necessary to fulfil any services that have been previously requested or may be required for accounting or other legal and regulatory purposes.
e) You have the right to limit or restrict processing of your data. Please note that this may cause issues with delivering services to you. Please contact us to discuss any concerns you have regarding the processing of your data.
f) You have the right to data portability. You may request that data we hold about you is transferred to another organisation. Please email us at: This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it. or write to our registered address below with details of the transfer required.
We will always endeavour to uphold your rights regarding the processing of your personal data and address any concerns you have regarding the processing of your data. However, if you feel that we have not complied sufficiently with your requests please contact the ICO (Information Commissioners Office) who is the supervisory authority for all data issues in the United Kingdom.
5. Security
Wessex Institute of Technology is committed to ensuring your information is protected and held securely. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect. However, the internet is not a secure medium and Wessex Institute of Technology cannot accept responsibility for security of an e-mail during transmission or for non-delivery of that e-mail.
6. Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, if you use these links you will leave our website and you should note that we do not have any control over the accuracy of the information presented or the processes implemented by other websites. Therefore we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting other websites and such websites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Registered address:
Data OfficerWessex Institute of TechnologyAshurst LodgeAshurstSouthamptonSO40 7AAUnited Kingdom
Wessex Institute Ashurst Lodge, Ashurst, Southampton SO40 7AA, UK Tel: +44 (0)238 029 3223 Fax: +44 (0)238 029 2853 Email: wit@wessex.ac.uk
Translation tool powered by Google. Wessex Institute is not responsible for incorrect translation.
Site Map | Privacy Policy
